Inventory of the BBC World Service Vietnamese radio broadcast recordings
Hoover Institution Archives
BBC World Service Vietnamese radio broadcast recordings
1963-2002
2014C7
Hoover Institution Archives
2 manuscript boxes, 11 oversize boxes, digital files (5.4 linear feet)
Sound recordings of radio broadcasts to Vietnam. Includes some radio scripts and background newspaper clippings.
BBC World Service.
Access
The collection is open for research. The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2013.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
The BBC World Service (Asia Hub) ended radio broadcasting in March 2011. It included Chinese, Indonesian, Thai, and Vietnamese language services.
Scope and Contents note
Sound recordings of radio broadcasts to Vietnam. Includes some radio scripts and background newspaper clippings. Titles of sound recordings are from tape labels.
Audiotapes.; Radio broadcasting--Vietnam.
Collection Contents
- Radio scripts and background newspaper clippings (Box 1-2)
- Sound recordings, 1969, 1973-2004; 655 sound tape reels (Box 3-11, digital files)
  Consists of significant radio broadcast recordings. Among those featured are Nguyen Thi Bihn, Bui Tin, Pham Dry, and Trinh Cong Song. 342 reels, selected for their significance by Hoover staff, have been digitized for use and listed here.
  - Vietnam in 1996, 23 December 1996 (Tape 1)
    22:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6AFDA960_Vietnamin1996(1)
  - Vietnam Doi Moi 2, 23 April 1997 (Tape 2)
    Summary: 10th year anniversary of Doi Moi, 19:18 minutes. Use copy reference number: FB83FEF1_VietnamDoiMoi2
  - Vietnam Doi Moi 3, 2 May 1997 (Tape 3)
    Summary: 10th year anniversary of Doi Moi, 19:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6BAD6941_VietnamDoiMoi3
  - Nong Duc Manh fights corruption, unknown (Tape 4)
    Summary: Nong Duc Manh, corruption, unknown minutes. Use copy reference number: BBBC17B1_NongDucManhfightscorruption
  - Year of Anniversaries, 6 April 1985 (Tape 5)
    Summary: 30th anniversary of French evacuation of Haiphong with Ralph Smith, 9:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: ABD50686_YearofAnniversaries
  - Vietnam: Ten years on, 30 April 1985 (Tape 6)
    Summary: 10th anniversary of end of war, 12:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3BEB4610_VietnamTenYearsOn
  - Dai Hoi 8, 17 July 1997 (Tape 7)
    Summary: 8th Communist Party Congress. Use copy reference number: FBFDE8D1_DaiHoi8-1
  - Dai Hoi 8, 17 July 1997 (Tape 8)
    Summary: 8th Communist Party Congress. Use copy reference number: 7C122E57_DaiHoi8-2
  - Dai Hoi 8, unknown (Tape 9)
    Summary: 8th Communist Party Congress.
  - 75 Years of the BBC, 15 December 1997 (Tape 10)
    20:37 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6C42436B_75YearsoftheBBC
  - Cardinal Nguyen Van Thuan (Tape 11)
    Summary: Profiles, Week 38: Catholicism, Nguyen Van Thuan, 11:23 minutes. Use copy reference number: AC4FE9AE_NguyenVanThuan
  - Interview with Mrs. Nguyen Thi Binh, 7 January 1973 (Tape 12)
    Use copy reference number: AC664386_InterviewNguyenThiBinh
  - Interview with Tran Do, 28 June 2002 (Tape 13)
    Summary: Tran Do, dissident, 16:46 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6DE4C543_InterviewTuongTranDo
  - Interview with Dr. Nguyen Dan Que, 26 July 2002 (Tape 14)
    Summary: Nguyen Dan Que, dissident, 17:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FDFFABFC_InterviewBSNguyenDanQue
  - Interview with Tran Van Lam, former South Vietnam minister, 27 January 1973 (Tape 15)
    Summary: Tran Van Lam, South Vietnam, 9:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3E1BF515_InterviewTranVanLam
  - Mai Am Gia Dinh (Tape 16)
    Summary: women, family, 11:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: 2E3EF501_MaiAmGiaDinh
  - Islam 1 (Tape 26a)
    Summary: Islam, 23:13 minutes.
  - Islam 2 (Tape 27)
    Summary: Islam, 22:45 minutes.
  - Islam 3 (Tape 28)
    Summary: Islam, 23:55 minutes.
  - Islam 4 (Tape 29)
    Summary: Islam, 22:13 minutes.
  - Islam 5 (Tape 30)
    Summary: Islam, 22:40 minutes.
  - ASEAN (Tape 45)
    Summary: ASEAN, 23:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: BE67BF92_ASEAN
  - Spy R Us 2 (Tape 47)
    Summary: espionage, 21:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: B13E5B9D_SpyRUs2
  - Diplomatic Jigsaw 3 (Tape 48)
    23:42 minutes. Use copy reference number: 71ABBA45_DiplomaticJigsaw3
  - Spy R Us 3 (Tape 49)
    Summary: espionage, 22:28 minutes. Use copy reference number: B15781BD_SpyRUs3
  - Vietnam or not 2 (Tape 50)
    24:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 71C59362_Vietnamornot2
  - The American Story 1 (Tape 82)
    Summary: U.S.-Vietnam relations. Use copy reference number: B1DD4C8A_TheAmericanStory1
  - The American Story 2 (Tape 83)
    Summary: U.S.-Vietnam relations. Use copy reference number: F1F0E2E9_TheAmericanStory2
  - The American Story 3 (Tape 84)
    Summary: U.S.-Vietnam relations, 17:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: F20413FB_TheAmericanStory3
  - Agenda Week 9, 3 March 2001 (Tape 85)
    15:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: F25558F0_Agenda9Espionage
  - Agenda Week 24 (Tape 86)
    Summary: Zen Buddhism, Thich Nhat Hanh, 16:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: F26889E9_Agenda24ThichNhatHanh
  - Agenda Censorship (Tape 87)
    Summary: censorship, 16:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 72832474_AgendaCensorship
  - Tet Story (Tape 97)
    Summary: Lunar New Year, 22:28 minutes. Use copy reference number: 72934550_TetStory
  - Vietnamese in Cambodia 1, 16 October 1998 (Tape 98)
    Summary: Vietnamese in Cambodia, 19:24 minutes. Use copy reference number: 72C43D6E_VietnameseinCambodia1
  - Vietnamese in Cambodia 2 (Tape 99)
    Summary: Vietnamese in Cambodia, 19:17 minutes. Use copy reference number: F806E876_VietnameseinCambodia2
  - Vietnamese (Tape 103)
    Use copy reference number: C85FA0C3_UnknownVietnamese1
  - Tet Story, 15 February 1999 (Tape 104)
    Summary: lunar new year, 18:24 minutes. Use copy reference number: C876F7C8_TetStory2
  - Bao Chi Hai Ngoai (Tape 105)
    Summary: foreign newspapers. Use copy reference number: D8C5FE55_BaoChiHaiNgoai
  - Vietnam and Globalisation 4, 28 October 2001 (Tape 107)
    Summary: globalization, U.S.-Vietnam relations, 10:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: C97195C4_VietnamandGlobalization4
  - Hoi Huong 1 (Tape 113)
    Use copy reference number: C984308A_HoiHuong1
  - Hoi Huong 2, 3 March 1996 (Tape 114)
    Use copy reference number: E990F8A4_HoiHuong2
  - Hoi Huong 3, 10 March 1996 (Tape 115)
    20:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: C9ABD443_HoiHuong3
  - Vietnam Social and Political Program 2 (Tape 116)
    Use copy reference number: C9C6CA04_VietnamSocialandPolitical2
  - Saigon 10 Years ago, 29 April 1985 (Tape 117)
    5:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F9DD9833_Saigon10Yearsago
  - Le Kha Phieu in Cuba (Tape 121)
    Summary: Le Kha Phieu, VN-Cuba relations. Use copy reference number: C9F06087_LeKhaPhieuinCuba
  - Do The Chi (Tape 122)
    Use copy reference number: EA050CE6_DoTheChi
  - Viet Leaders 4 (Tape 123)
    Use copy reference number: EA1B7EA2_VietLeaders
  - Ho Si Thoang (Tape 124)
    Use copy reference number: FA2A8933_HoSiThoang
  - Nhac Sinh Vien Paris 2 (Tape 130)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: CA49A180_NhacSinhVienParis
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 1 (Tape 131)
    Summary: poetry, 15:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: DEBCF753_VietnamesePoetry1
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 2 (Tape 132)
    Summary: poetry, 14:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: CF18444D_VietnamesePoetry2
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 3 (Tape 133)
    Summary: poetry, 12:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: EF23B1A8_VietnamesePoetry3
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 4 (Tape 134)
    Summary: poetry, 13:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: CF34B902_VietnamesePoetry4
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 5 (Tape 135)
    Summary: poetry, 13:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: CF473A43_VietnamesePoetry5
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 6 (Tape 136)
    Summary: poetry, 12:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: DF54709E_VietnamesePoetry6
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 7 (Tape 137)
    Summary: poetry, 12:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: CF5E424C_VietnamesePoetry7
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 8 (Tape 138)
    Summary: poetry, 13:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: DF69FF51_VietnamesePoetry8
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 9 (Tape 139)
    Summary: poetry, 13:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: DF7512DA_VietnamesePoetry9
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 10 (Tape 140)
    Summary: poetry, 13:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: DF7F461C_VietnamesePoetry10
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 11 (Tape 141)
    Summary: poetry, 15:24 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF8C8ABB_VietnamesePoetry11
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 12 (Tape 142)
    Summary: poetry, 13:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: FFB3B438_VietnamesePoetry12
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 13, 20 July 1983 (Tape 143)
    Summary: poetry, 14:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FFC07179_VietnamesePoetry13
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 14, 20 July 1983 (Tape 144)
    Summary: poetry, 12:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: DFCBAD93_VietnamesePoetry14
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, program 15, 20 July 1983 (Tape 145)
    Summary: poetry, 13:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: FFDEC7F0_VietnamesePoetry15
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, program 16, 20 July 1983 (Tape 146)
    Summary: poetry, 13:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: DFFBA319_VietnamesePoetry16
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 17, 27 October 1983 (Tape 147)
    Summary: poetry, 15:18 minutes. Use copy reference number: D00A4701_VietnamesePoetry17
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 18, 27 October 1983 (Tape 148)
    Summary: poetry, 15:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: D016EAC8_VietnamesePoetry18
  - Half a Century of Vietnamese Poetry, program 19, 27 October 1983 (Tape 149)
    Summary: poetry, 14:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: F022037B_VietnamesePoetry19
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 20, 25 November 1983 (Tape 150)
    Summary: poetry, 14:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: D02DA61D_VietnamesePoetry20
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 21 (Tape 151)
    Summary: poetry, 17:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: F0424425_VietnamesePoetry21
  - Half Century of Vietnamese Poetry, Program 22, 25 November 1983 (Tape 152)
    Summary: poetry, 17:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: D04D079D_VietnamesePoetry22
  - Arts Mag, Tan Nhac Vietnam, 20 December 1999 (Tape 153)
    Summary: music, 9:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: D16E1E58_ArtsMag
  - Theatre Magazine, 2 December 1975 (Tape 154)
    Summary: theatre. Use copy reference number: D188D5DA_TheatreMagazine
  - Pham Duy 1940-1950, part 1 (Tape 155)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy.
  - Pham Duy 1940-1950, part (Tape 155a)
  - Pham Duy 1950-1960, part 2 (Tape 156)
  - Pham Duy, 1950-1960, part 3 (Tape 157)
  - Music (Tape 158)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: D1E7504D_Music
  - Tran Van Trach (Tape 159)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: F21533AB_TranVanTrach
  - Music, 13 February 1969 (Tape 160)
    Summary: music, Trinh Cong Son?. Use copy reference number: D2584AC6_Music2
  - Dao Ca (Tape 161)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: 7E428A5A_DaoCa
  - Bach Yen Dan Ca (Tape 167)
    Summary: folk music. Use copy reference number: 2E7EFF04_BachYenDanCa
  - Saigon Vinh Biet, 2 December 1983 (Tape 180)
    Summary: music, 17:47 minutes. Use copy reference number: F1F5BB78_SaigonVinhBiet
  - Hop xuong Hai Linh (Tape 181)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: AF1909A9_HopXuongHaiLinh
  - Tet Music Program, 1 February 1980 (Tape 182)
    Summary: music, 19:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF26D0DA_TetMusicProgram
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 1, 7 December 1997 (Tape 183)
    Summary: music, 19:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: EF3DDFED_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam1
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 2, 14 December 1997 (Tape 184)
    Summary: music, 21:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3F4C251D_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam2
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 3, 21 December 1997 (Tape 185)
    Summary: music, 19:59 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF5A94D9_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam3
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 4, 28 December 1997 (Tape 186)
    Summary: music, 19:06 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3F6E813D_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam4
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 5, 4 January 1998 (Tape 187)
    Summary: music, 20:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: EF92E0C2_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam5
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 6, 11 January 1998 (Tape 188)
    Summary: music, 19:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: AF9F6482_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam6
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 7, 18 January 1998 (Tape 189)
    Summary: music, 20:04 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3FB15614_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam7
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 8 (Tape 190)
    Summary: music, 19:16 minutes. Use copy reference number: 2FC9172A_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam8
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 9 (Tape 191)
    Summary: music, 20:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: AFDAD18F_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam9
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 10, 8 November 1997 (Tape 191a)
    Summary: music, 19:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: EFED77C9_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam10
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 11, 15 February 1998 (Tape 192)
    Summary: music, 21:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3FFBFE18_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam11
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 12, 22 February 1998 (Tape 193)
    Summary: music, 19:54 minutes. Use copy reference number: 300AFD05_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam12
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 13, 1 March 1998 (Tape 194)
    Summary: music, 18:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7018B54A_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam13
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 14, 8 March 1998 (Tape 195)
    Summary: music, 20:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7025B858_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam14
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 15, 15 March 1998 (Tape 196)
    Summary: music, 20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F044FDC6_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam15
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 16, 22 March 1998 (Tape 197)
    Summary: music, 19:07 minutes. Use copy reference number: F053B2FC_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam16
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 17, 29 March 1998 (Tape 198)
    Summary: music, 20:14 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7063C37E_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam17
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 18, 5 April 1998 (Tape 199)
    Summary: music, 21:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7074044A_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam18
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 19, 12 April 1998 (Tape 200)
    Summary: music, 20:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: B088BD81_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam19
  - Suoi Nguon Tan Nhac Vietnam 20, 19 April 1998 (Tape 201)
    Summary: music, 20:12 minutes. Use copy reference number: 709CE54D_SuoiNguonTanNhacVietnam20
  - Vietnamese Children's Party, 5 December 1982 (Tape 207)
    Use copy reference number: 7174D240_VietnameseChildren
  - Hoang Phu Ngoc Tuong and My Da (Tape 225)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: 79E0037D_HoangPhuNgocThuong&MyDa
  - Tran Van Khe 1, 1 August 1976 (Tape 245)
    Summary: folk music, Tran Van Khe. Use copy reference number: F184F2D9_TranVanKhe1
  - Tran Van Khe 2, 1 August 1976 (Tape 246)
    Summary: folk music, Tran Van Khe. Use copy reference number: F19884E9_TranVanKhe2
  - Tran Van Khe 3, 1 August 1976 (Tape 247)
    Summary: folk music, Tran Van Khe. Use copy reference number: F1AC0ECB_TranVanKhe3
  - Tran Van Khe 4 (Tape 248)
    Summary: folk music, Tran Van Khe. Use copy reference number: F1C12DEC_TranVanKhe4
  - Tran Van Khe, 13 August 1976 (Tape 249)
    Summary: folk music, Tran Van Khe. Use copy reference number: B1D3FABA_TranVanKhe5
  - Ngo Thuy Mien (Tape 250)
    Summary: music, Ngo Thuy Mien. Use copy reference number: B20B6281_NgoThuyMien1
  - Ngo Thuy Mien 2 (A) (Tape 251)
    Summary: music, Ngo Thuy Mien. Use copy reference number: 3237B400_NgoThuyMien2A
  - Ngo Thuy Mien 2 (A) (Tape 251)
    Summary: music, Ngo Thuy Mien.
  - Ngo Thuy Mien 2 (B), music, Ngo Thuy Mien (Tape 252)
    Use copy reference number: 3247F825_NgoThuyMien2B
  - Ngo Thuy Mien 2 (B) (Tape 252)
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 1 (Tape 253)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 17:41 minutes. Use copy reference number: B7735FA6_PhamDuyMemoirs1
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 2 (Tape 254)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 17:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7782DD4B_PhamDuyMemoirs2
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 3 (Tape 255)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 17:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3790BB3F_PhamDuyMemoirs3
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 4 (Tape 256)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 17:11 minutes. Use copy reference number: B79E12AD_PhamDuyMemoirs4
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 5 (Tape 257)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 17:57 minutes. Use copy reference number: B7ACA9BB_PhamDuyMemoirs5
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 6 (Tape 258)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: 37BA470E_PhamDuyMemoirs6
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 7 (Tape 259)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: F7C86EDF_PhamDuyMemoirs7
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 8, 10 August 1991 (Tape 260)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: B7D98AA8_PhamDuyMemoirs8
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 9 (Tape 261)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: 37E7D215_PhamDuyMemoirs9
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 10 (Tape 262)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7809AC5C_PhamDuyMemoirs10
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 11, 7 September 1991 (Tape 263)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: F820F4DF_PhamDuyMemoirs11
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 12, 14 September 1991 (Tape 264)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: 382E7402_PhamDuyMemoirs12
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 13 (Tape 265)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:21 minutes. Use copy reference number: 383C1430_PhamDuyMemoirs13
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 14 (Tape 266)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:18 minutes. Use copy reference number: 784DD441_PhamDuyMemoirs14
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 15 (Tape 267)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: F86A57DF_PhamDuyMemoirs15
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 16, 12 October 1991 (Tape 268)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: B8978AA2_PhamDuyMemoirs16
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 17, 19 October 1991 (Tape 269)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:13 minutes. Use copy reference number: 78B0FF5E_PhamDuyMemoirs17
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 18, 26 October 1991 (Tape 270)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: 78BE7C71_PhamDuyMemoirs18
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 19, 2 November 1991 (Tape 271)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: B8CC498A_PhamDuyMemoirs19
  - Pham Duy Memoirs 20, 9 November 1991 (Tape 272)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 18:03 minutes. Use copy reference number: 38DBFC01_PhamDuyMemoirs20
  - Pham Duy 1940-1950 (Tape 273)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 26:16 minutes.
  - Pham Duy 1940-1950 (Tape 274)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 24:15 minutes.
  - Pham Duy 1950-1960 (Tape 275)
  - Nhac Tinh Pham Duy (Tape 276)
  - Pham Duy 1, 26 July 1982 (Tape 277)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 15:45 minutes.
  - Pham Duy 3 (Tape 278)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 16:05 minutes.
  - Pham Duy 1 and 2 (Tape 279)
  - Pham Duy 3 and 4 (Tape 279a)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 7:50 minutes.
  - Pham Duy (Tape 280)
    Summary: music, Pham Duy, 2:40 minutes.
  - Cultural Revolution 1, 23 September 1996 (Tape 281)
    Summary: China, history, 21:18 minutes. Use copy reference number: 78F47450_CulturalRevolution1
  - Cultural Revolution 2, 30 September 1996 (Tape 282)
    Summary: China, history, 21:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: 39058A04_CulturalRevolution2
  - Cultural Revolution 3 (Tape 283)
    Summary: China, history, 20:37 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7919EB7D_CulturalRevolution3
  - Cultural Revolution 4, 8 November 1996 (Tape 284)
    Summary: China, history, 20:42 minutes. Use copy reference number: B9295694_CulturalRevolution4
  - Cultural Revolution 5, 14 November 1996 (Tape 285)
    Summary: China, history, 19:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: F93900FD_CulturalRevolution5
  - Cultural Revolution 6, 22 November 1996 (Tape 286)
    Summary: China, history, 19:58 minutes. Use copy reference number: 39480D2F_CulturalRevolution6
  - Rock and Roll Years, 30 October 1996 (Tape 298)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 21:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: B3CAECA7_RockandRoll1
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1954, 18 November 1994 (Tape 299)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 17:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: F3E9D2F3_RockandRoll1954
  - Rock and Roll Years, 4 December 1996 (Tape 300)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 33DD4F37_RockandRoll2
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1957, 16 December 1994 (Tape 301)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: 33F9970F_RockandRoll1957
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1958, 23 December 1994 (Tape 302)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:46 minutes. Use copy reference number: B41036B4_RockandRoll1958
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1959, 30 December 1994 (Tape 303)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 23:16 minutes. Use copy reference number: F4371DD6_RockandRoll1959
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1960, 13 January 1995 (Tape 304)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: F446B7C5_RockandRoll1960
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1961, 10 February 1995 (Tape 305)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: F45474D3_RockandRoll1961
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1962 (Tape 306)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 16:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 746A8A40_RockandRoll1962
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1963 (Tape 307)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 18:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 347F9830_RockandRoll1963
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1964, 24 February 1995 (Tape 308)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 19:37 minutes. Use copy reference number: B48E23A0_RockandRoll1964
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1965, 24 February 1995 (Tape 309)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 17:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: 749B8768_RockandRoll1965
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1966, 24 February 1995 (Tape 310)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 21:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: 74B0F546_RockandRoll1966
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1967, 2 February 1995 (Tape 311)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 21:12 minutes. Use copy reference number: B4C0A2B4_RockandRoll1967
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1968, 3 March 1995 (Tape 312)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 22:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: B4CF5B9E_RockandRoll1968
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1969, 3 March 1995 (Tape 313)